enmasse.com 2019-06-23

# Privacy Policy - En Masse Entertainment

EULA | Terms of Service | Privacy Policy | Rules of Conduct | Partner Rules of Conduct | Player-Created Content | Contest Rules

* * *

## Privacy and Cookie Policy

En masse Entertainment, Inc. (“En Masse”, “we”, or “our”) respects your privacy and is committed to protect the personal Information that you may provide us while using our sites located on the enmasse.com domain (the “Site”) and the services and features offered through the Site (the “Services”). This policy describes what information En Masse Collects when you use the Services and offered by En Masse. By using our Services, you consent to this policy.

### Table of Contents

  1. Information We Collect
  2. How We Collect Information
  3. How We Use Your Information
  4. Information We Share with Third Parties
  5. Where We Hold Your Information
  6. How We Protect Your Personal Information
  7. Children
  8. Your Choices and Controls
  9. Third Party Services
  10. Changes to Our Policy
  11. Contact Us

### 1\. Information We Collect

The information we collect depends on which service you use and how you use them. We collect two types of information; “personal information” that identifies you as a specific individual and “non-personal information” that doesn’t. The particular kinds of personal and non-personal information we collect usually depend on how you interact with us. The controller of the personal information collected is En Masse Entertainment, Inc., 1218 3rd Ave. Suite 800, Seattle, WA. 98101, USA.

#### A. Information You Give Us Directly

We collect information you provide us, including:

  * Your email address and password;
  * Security questions and answers;
  * Billing information such as your name, address, telephone number, payment card number, and payment account details;
  * Information you provide when seeking help from us such as your nickname or user-number and records of the issues you experience;
  * Demographic details, for instance in response to surveys about our services; and
  * Information you provide to enter a contest or sweepstakes. If you win, we may need to collect your social security number, postal address and/or national identification for eligibility, prizes delivery and tax purposes.

When you participate in social features (such as chat), the information that you disclose is public information. We may store and access it, and it may be read, copied, collected or used by other users without your consent. Please make sure your privacy settings reflect your preferences.

When you participate in online multi-play games, your in-game profile information, gameplay, and statistics are visible to all. We may record your gameplay, including your controller button inputs, and replay these together with your profile information and game statistics to other players in-game without further notice to you, for example as part of a spectator mode, or for out-of-game promotional purposes.

#### B. Other Information We Collect When You Use Our Services Automatically

We collect information automatically when you use our services, including:

  * Your Device Info (include OS system, OS version, screen resolution, browser type and setting, etc.),
  * IP address,
  * Data during our game play, and
  * Device event information, including crash reports and system activity details (e.g. whether you encountered an error playing our games or lost Internet access).

We also may collect information locally on your device, using mechanisms like Session Info such as keys for login, google analysis cookies, and application data caches.

#### C. Information Provided to Us by Third Parties

**PlayStation®4**. By signing up to play our services on a PlayStation®4, you agree your Sony Entertainment Network account information will be provided to En Masse From Sony, we receive information including your account (email address), item you purchased, data log for game play and item used and IP add. We do not receive your credit card number or other financial information.

**Xbox Live**. By signing up to play our services on Microsoft's Xbox Live Service, you agree that Microsoft may provide us with your Microsoft user account information. From Microsoft, we receive information including your account, item you purchased, data log for game play and item used and IP address. We do not receive your credit card number or other financial information.

**Other Third Parties**. We may receive your account information from third parties, like Facebook, when you use these services in connection with our services. We also may receive information from third parties to supplement the information we receive from you. We use information from these companies primarily to help us deliver relevant advertising and sending newsletter to you. We also may use information from third parties, for instance, to help us understand your approximate geolocation via your IP address for tax purposes, or to customize certain services to your location, and for fraud and/or abuse prevention purposes.

### 2\. How We Collect Information

We collect information from you when you provide it to us directly, such as via an online form on our website or when you summit your support ticket to our CS team through http://support.enmasse.com/games. And also we and third parties use certain technologies described below to collect information to deliver excellent experiences.

#### A. Cookies and Other Similar Tracking Technologies

Cookies are small text pieces of data that online services you use place on your device for record-keeping purposes and stored on your Internet browser. We use cookies and similar technologies to help us understand things like what web pages, features or ads you view and what games you play. This information helps us keep track of your purchased records, measure the effectiveness of our advertising, make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly and otherwise help enhance your user experience. You can disable cookies, limit the types of cookies you allow, or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent. Please refer to [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) or the guidance provided by your individual web browser if you'd like help in managing your cookie preferences.

We use other technologies for similar purposes as a cookie. We use Internet log files (which contain technical data such as your IP address) to monitor traffic on our services, troubleshoot technical problems, detect and prevent fraud and enforce our User Agreement.

#### B. Analytics Technologies

We use our own game servers and internal and third party analytic technologies to collect information about how you use our services, your device and the health of our services.

For instance, En Masse may collect and store data from your device when you use our services. This information includes technical and related information about your device info (such as operating system information and IP Address), information about your feature usage, gameplay and usage statistics. If you participate in online services, En Masse also may collect, use, store, transmit and publicly display statistical data regarding game play (including scores, rankings and accomplishments), or identify content that is created and shared by you with other players.

#### C. Advertisement Serving Technologies

Some of our services employ advertisement serving technologies that use cookies and other similar technologies like identifiers to deliver offers to you. The ads can be tailored to your interests. For instance, you may be presented with an offer for a game we think you might enjoy. Or if you express interest in a game, you might be offered an advertisement later for that game or similar services on En Masse or 3rd party’s web sites.

The 3rd parties’ services via their web sites collect and use information under their own privacy policies.

These technologies of the 3rd parties collect and use information so we can serve appropriate advertising to you and help track results and measure effectiveness. In addition to identifiers, this information includes:

  * Advertisements served and the location of the ad;
  * Domain type, IP address; and
  * Advertisement response for target marketing.

The 3rd party companies may combine the information collected in the context of delivering an ad to you via our Services with other information they have independently collected across their websites. 

To learn more about some of these ad networks' practices, or to opt out of third party targeted advertising, you can visit [ https://www.networkadvertising.org](https://www.networkadvertising.org/), <https://www.aboutads.info/choices/>, <http://youradchoices.ca/>, or [https://www.youronlinechoices.eu](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/). Note that opting out does not mean you won't see ads; it just means that the advertising you see may be less relevant to your interests.

#### D. Anti-Cheat and Fraud Prevention Technologies

En Masse strives to provide a safe and fair gaming environment for all players. When you log in to one of our services, set up an En Masse Account or make purchases, we or third parties may use cookies and similar technologies, or collect data about your machine or device, to create a machine "fingerprint" or "hash" of your machine components, for fraud prevention, security and authentication purposes. We also may use other anti-cheat technology with our services.

### 3\. How We Use Your Information

We use your personal and non-personal information, both individually and combined together, in the following ways:

#### A. To operate our business and to enhance and personalize your game experience including to:

  * Operate, improve, and develop our games and services;
  * Help you find your friends or tell your friends about an En Masse service;
  * Facilitate sharing on social networks;
  * Serve and measure the effectiveness of advertising;
  * Measure the health of our services;
  * Set up and maintain accounts you register for;
  * Provide game experiences that you may like;
  * Facilitate your gameplay on multiple devices when available;
  * Identify, fix, and troubleshoot bugs and service errors;
  * Provide software updates;
  * Offer you to purchase EMP(currency to purchase related to our games and services)
  * Activate or authenticate your games and save game progress and stats; and
  * Help keep our services safe and fair, resolve disputes, investigate and help curb fraud and illegal behavior, comply with the law, and to enforce our agreements and policies.

#### B. To provide you support, including to:

  * Help identify and troubleshoot problems with your account or games;
  * To survey your opinions through surveys or questionnaires; and
  * Manage and send you confirmations and important information about your account, services, purchases, subscriptions, and warranties.

#### C. To personalize our communications with you, including to:

  * Present offers and/or information relating to games you might like;
  * Make recommendations to you; and
  * Personalize advertising for you and deliver targeted marketing, service updates and promotional offers.

We do not share personal information in principle that directly identifies you (such as your name, e-mail or postal address) with independent third parties without your consent, unless it is either required by law or we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our rights, property or operations or to protect our players or third parties. We may share anonymous or other data that does not directly identify you, with third parties, for instance to show trends about use of our services.

We might employ third parties located in and outside of your country of residence (including outside of the European Economic Area (EEA)) to collect or process personal information on our behalf for various reasons, such as maintaining our service, offering promotion/marketing or sending emails. When our third party agents or service providers collect or receive personal information, we require that they use the data only on our behalf and for purposes consistent with this policy.

We do not knowingly disclose personal information about children under 18 years of age to independent third parties even with consent.

However, in the event of a reorganization, divestiture, merger, sale or bankruptcy, we may transfer all information we collect to the relevant third party and will obtain your consent to do so if required by law.

We do not control information sent from your browser to third parties, such as advertising networks and analytics companies that receive information in the normal course of your Internet activity. When third party technologies or social tools are integrated into our services, those third parties may collect information when you use our services. An example is the Facebook "Like" button.

We remain responsible for the processing of personal information received under the Privacy Shield frameworks and subsequently transferred to a third party acting as an agent if the agent processes such personal information in a manner inconsistent with the principles, unless we prove that we are not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage. We may be required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

### 5\. Where We Hold Your Information

We maintain servers around the world and your information may be processed on servers located outside of the country where you live. Data protection laws vary among countries, with some providing more protection than others. Regardless of where your information is processed, we apply the same protections described in this policy. By using our services, you expressly agree that your personal and non-personal data may be processed and stored outside of the country you live and used for the purposes described in this policy.

### 6\. How We Protect Your Personal Information

Security of our players' information is a priority at En Masse, and we take a range of measures to help protect it, including pseudonymisation like encryption of sensitive information, and activities like prevention, monitoring and recovery of security incident for business continuity management. Even so, no security measure is perfect. This means we cannot guarantee the security of your information and do not assume any responsibility for the unauthorized use or access to your information under our control.

### 7\. Children

Protecting children's privacy online is extremely important to En Masse. Many En Masse services are intended for general audiences and do not knowingly collect any personal information from children.

If you under the age of 13(or under the minimum age in the relevant territory), you may not create an account on the site. We will not knowingly collect, maintain, or disclose any personal information from children under the age of 13. 

If you are between the ages of thirteen(13) and eighteen(18), your parent or guardian must consent to your use of our services and take full responsibility for all obligations under this Privacy Policy and Terms of Service.

En Masse does not allow children under the age of 18 to use our services without the consent of their parents. En Masse complies with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and all other applicable laws and regulations concerning children and the Internet. We do not disclose any Personal Information about children under 18 years of age who have registered on the Site to third parties, or share or disclose Personal Information other than as set forth in this Privacy Policy; provided however, that in the event of a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, or similar transaction, management of our customer information may be transferred to our successor or assign.

Information collected is secured in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy (see Section 6 above). 

Please note that if you grant consent for your child to use En Masse's services, this may include such general audience communication services as email, instant messaging, and forum, and your child will be able to communicate with, and disclose personal information to, other users of all ages. We encourage you to talk with your children about communicating with strangers and disclosing personal information online.

If you are a parent and wish to revoke your previously provided consent, review information collected from your child or have that information deleted, contact the appropriate [support.enmasse.com](http://support.enmasse.com/games).

If we make material changes to how we use, collect, or share your child's personal information, we will notify parents by email or by in-game notice in order to obtain verifiable parental consent for the new uses of your child's personal information.

### 8\. Your Choices and Controls

We give you meaningful choices when it comes to important uses and collection of information. For example, you can update your account information and preferences, choose to opt in or out of newsletters and Account Armor™, and choose whether to save your payment method. If you want at any time after granting approval, you can opt in or out and review and change most of your preferences through your En Masse Account settings. If you need additional assistance, please contact [support.enmasse.com/games](http://support.enmasse.com/games).

You may deactivate your En Masse Account or delete the personal information associated with your account by contacting [support.enmasse.com/games](http://support.enmasse.com/games) or your Personal Information Protection Officer. If you do so, you will no longer have access to the En Masse games or services associated with your account. Note that En Masse may retain information needed to resolve disputes, enforce our user agreements, protect our legal rights, and comply with technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of our services. Otherwise, we will retain your personal information for as long as reasonably necessary to provide you services, create and improve our services, comply with the law, and to run our business. The Information retained is secured in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy (see Section 6 above).

You have rights of access, rectification, erasure, restriction and object of processing and data portability for the personal information we hold about you. To request your rights, contact [support.enmasse.com/games](http://support.enmasse.com/games). Before we process any request, we may ask you for certain personal information in order to verify your identity and we may request payment where allowed by law. Where permitted by local law, we may reject requests that are unreasonable or impractical. We will respond to your requests in a reasonable timeframe.

You also may adjust your browser settings to block certain online tracking, such as cookies. (see Section 2.A above).

### 9\. Third Party Services

Our websites and services may contain advertising or third party services (such as the Facebook Like button or links to third-party websites). If you click on those links, including an advertisement, you will leave the En Masse website and go to the site you selected. If you visit a third party website or use a third party service, you should consult that site's or service's privacy policy.

### 10\. Changes to Our Policy

We may update this policy from time to time, so please review it frequently. We'll notify you of material changes via a notice on our home page (www.enmasse.com) thirty days before they go into effect. Your continued use of our services means you accept the changes. Once you accept this policy, we will not enforce future changes we deem in good faith to be material absent your express agreement to the changed terms. If you are asked to affirmatively accept material changes to this policy and you decline to do so, you may not be able to continue to use the service provided.

### 11\. Contact Us

If you have a complaint or question about this policy, you may contact us through [support.enmasse.com/games](http://support.enmasse.com/games) If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact Personal Information Protection Officer.

#### Post:

Personal Information Protection Officer  
En Masse Entertainment  
1218 3rd Ave Suite 800  
Seattle, WA 98101 

#### Online:

Personal Information Protection Officer email: [privacy@enmasse.com](mailto:privacy@enmasse.com)

VeraSafe has been appointed as En Masse Entertainments's representative in the European Union for data protection matters, pursuant to Article 27 of the General Data Protection Regulation of the European Union. VeraSafe can be contacted in addition to our Personal Information Protection Officer, only on matters related to the processing of personal data. To make such an inquiry, please contact VeraSafe using this contact form: [https://www.verasafe.com/privacy-services/contact-article-27-representative](https://www.verasafe.com/privacy-services/contact-article-27-representative/)

Alternatively, VeraSafe can be contacted at:

**Matthew Joseph**   
Zahradníčkova 1220/20A  
Prague 15000  
Czech Republic

**VeraSafe Ireland Ltd**   
Unit 3D North Point House  
North Point Business Park  
New Mallow Road  
Cork T23AT2P  
Ireland

En Masse has further committed to refer unresolved Privacy Shield complaints to TRUSTe, an alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States and the EU. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not resolved your complaint, please contact or visit [TRUSTe (https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request)). for more information or to file a complaint. The services of TRUSTe are provided at no cost to you.

For residual complaints not fully or partially resolved by other means, you may be able to invoke binding arbitration before the Privacy Shield Panel as detailed in the Principles.

For more information and updates to this policy, visit <http://www.enmasse.com/legal/privacy-policy>
